

#### **PROFILE**

Solution-driven Web Developer who is adept at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment.

Finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction.

Built products for desktop and web app users over 6+ years, meeting the highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices, and speed.

Possess strong attention to detail, well-developed time management skills, and the ability to complete all projects within schedule and in a timely manner.

# **CONTACT**

EMAIL:

arian.mobarghei@gmail.com

PHONE:

+98 912 517 6301

LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/arian-mobarghei-10697313b

GITHUB:

github.com/arian22

WEBSITE:

 $\underline{\text{aratsystem.ir}}$ 

## **PORTFOLIO**

https://arian22.github.io/portfolio/

# ARIAN MOBARGHEI

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Full Stack Developer**

**Vesta Wealth Partners** (2020 - Present)

Building and developing the new client portal for three branches.

redbarnportal.ca clients.pliriswealth.com westawealth.partners

Technology: Django & Python & Postgres & AWS

#### **Full Stack Developer**

Self-employed (2019 - 2020)

Developed a web application, "<u>aratsystem.ir</u>" for restaurants that allow customers to scan the menu and order their food.

Developed a web application for individual gold-retailer to trade gold from their wholesale. (over 1,000+ deals per day) demo video

Technology: LAMP & Vue.js & Anime.js & Bootstrap

#### Web Developer

**Zarrin**, Tehran, Iran (2016 – 2019)

Developed an e-commerce web app, customer web portal

Launch a website for a local charity "taj-gol.ir"

Technology: LAMP & jQuery & Materialize

## Java Developer

**Zarrin**, Tehran, Iran (2014 – 2016)

Develop UIs with Swing, JavaFX, HTML, and CSS

Wrote SQL queries to retrieve data from the database using JDBC

Creating and running a service for selling goods in the local network

Technology: Java SE & Java FX & MySQL & Tomcat

## **EDUCATION**

# **Azad University**

June 2014

**Bachelor of Computer Engineering** 

#### **CHARACTERISTICS**

- Creativity & Hard worker
- Excellent listener
- Problem-Solving Abilities